export default [
  { front: "Exit 0", back: "Cape May" },
  { front: "Exit 4", back: "Wildwood" },
  { front: "Exit 6", back: "North Wildwood" },
  { front: "Exit 10", back: "Stone Harbor" },
  { front: "Exit 13", back: "Avalon" },
  { front: "Exit 17", back: "Seaâ€¯Isle City" },
  { front: "Exit 25", back: "Ocean City" },
  { front: "Exit 29", back: "Somers Point / Ocean City" },
  { front: "Exit 36", back: "Pleasantville / Northfield / Brigantine (near AC)" },
  { front: "Exit 38", back: "Atlantic City" },
  // Added towns north of Atlantic City along the Parkway
  { front: "Exit 63", back: "Long Beach Island" },
  { front: "Exit 82", back: "Seaside / Seaside Heights" },
  { front: "Exit 98", back: "Belmar / Point Pleasant Beach" },
  { front: "Exit 100", back: "Asbury Park / Ocean Grove / Bradley Beach" },
  { front: "Exit 105", back: "Long Branch / Seven Presidents Beach" },
];
